# Bonmar Guilleno

#### Web Developer

Programmer with 1+ year experience providing service through virtual assistance, implementing revisions for client website and polishing design of the website. A combination of 5+ years of personal experience and academic knowledge in computer hardwares, softwares and networks. Keen to details and ensures the tasks are completed correctly and on time.



guilleno.bonmar1@gmail.com



09514459911



Las Pinas City, Philippines



31 May, 1998

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Senior Website Builder Luxury Presence

03/2021 - 01/2023

Provider of marketing tools for Real Estate Agents in the USA.

 Utilizing expertise to carefully edit website content, ensuring its accuracy, engagement, and optimization for search engines. Through skillful customization of layouts, graphics, and typography. Striving to create visually impressive and user-friendly websites that leave a lasting impact on visitors.

### OA Intern

#### **Endsofttech Web Solutions**

11/2018 - 04/2019

Provider of digital marketing, web development, domain and hosting services.

#### Tasks

• Ensures the functionality and usability of the websites before it goes live to meet the customer's expectations. Main tasks is manual but not limited to finding bugs, UI/UX problems and web glitches.

### **EDUCATION**

### Technological University of the Philippines Ayala Blvd. corner San Marcelino St. Ermita, 1000 Manila, Philippines

2016 - 2020

#### Courses

 Bachelor of Technology in Information Technology (CoET-BTIT)

### De La Salle Santiago Zobel BRafeNHS

University Avenue Ayala Alabang Village, Muntinlupa City

2012 - 2016

**Education Level** 

High School

### **SKILLS**



### CERTIFICATION

#### Ethical Hacking (03/2023)

Introduction to Blue Teaming. A vast learning workshop that extends to learning how blue team works including information gathering, tools used, types of threat, types of cyber attacks and the basics of active directory.

#### First Responder (12/2021)

 For always being ready to go when needed and for being there to count on - Given by the Offshore Operation Executive and Team Leader/Revisions Pod Manager.

### 99% Perspiration Award (12/2021)

For willingness to put in the hard work - Given by the Offshore Operation Executive and Team Leader/Revisions Pod Manager.

## **PROJECTS**

#### V2 - V3 Platform Migration (01/2022 - 06/2022)

Migrating of client's old website into a newer version of the platform provided by the company. Mimicking V2 to the V3 platform but not limited to application of new ideas to improve the design while staying in the standard operating procedures.

### SOFT SKILLS

Good moral character **Problem Solver** Able to get along well with co-workers, do supervision and accept supervision Concerned with quality Taking important notes Ensure tasks are completed correctly and on time Will to take every training for skill growth Fast Learner through visual learning